bitbond.com 2018-12-26

# Bitbond

## I. Scope

Bitbond GmbH (hereinafter also referred to as “we”) is the provider responsible for this website and its sub-pages (hereinafter also referred to as “offer”). Bitbond GmbH uses this website to mediate loans between investors and borrowers. The following privacy statement explains the nature, the scope and the purposes of levying, processing and usage of personal data by Bitbond GmbH on our website and sub-pages.

## II. The input of data by you

### 1\. Personal data and its usage

Personal data is specific information about personal or factual circumstances of an identified or identifiable natural person. These include the name, the e-mail address or the phone number. As part of our offer, personal data is only levied, processed and used where applicable and as permitted by law, or you have given consent. The same applies to the disclosure of personal data.

### 2\. Cookies

Our offer causes the storage of cookies on your browser. Cookies are text files that help to facilitate our offer, by storing Login data or registering when and how frequently you visit our offer. The storing of cookies can be disabled completely in all major browsers.

### 3\. Making contact

Our offer enables you to establish contact to us. This is possible, for example by sending an email to us. The information you provide while contacting us is stored, in order to process the request and, where appropriate, the following correspondence.

### 4\. Comments and contributions

Our offer also contains areas where the possibility of commenting is present (the blog and individual loan listings). To protect ourselves from illegal content, we store your IP-address if you leave a comment or comment on your own, or the comments of other individuals.

In order to allow discussion in our blog to flourish, you are given the opportunity to subscribe to the comments on your comments. This is done by entering your own email address. In order to ensure that the person who enters the email address is the owner of the email address, we send a confirmation email to the entered email address, which also contains information on how to unsubscribe. We also store the IP address and the date of the subscription, in order to prevent potential abuse. The data necessary to register for the subscription and email transmission is not used for other purposes or forwarded to third parties. The consent for the storage of this data can be revoked any time by sending an email to the provider or by clicking the link contained in every information email.

### 6\. Registration function

You can register as a user of our offer on the relevant and pertaining website pages, as an investor or borrower. The data received will be used here for the use of our offer. The utilisation also takes place, to inform you about changes in the scope of our offer or technical changes via email. The registration includes the entry of the following data:

  * Gender
  * First name
  * Last name
  * Emai laddress
  * address if applicable.

Beyond this, the IP-address used to register, as well as the date of the registration, are stored in order to prevent abuse of the registration function.

### 7\. "Initial Registration"

After registering an account as a "Borrower" or "Lender" you can utilise our offer as a user by choosing between "Get a Loan" or rather "Complete your lender registration" in the function area. The hereby provided data is used for the mediation, conclusion and implementation of the loan agreements (see our terms and conditions), as well as the fulfilment regulatory obligations, particularly of guidelines for prevention of money laundering and, if this is necessary for the use of our services, transmitted to other users.

## III. Visiting our Website

In addition to the entering of personal data, data is collected by us and third parties automatically during the utilisation of our offer. The use of our service includes interacting with third parties.

### 1\. Access Data/Server Log Files

Your visit to our site is stored in a log file (so-called server log files). To this end, we collect (or our internet provider) the following data on each access to our offer:

  * IP address of the accessing computer
  * Name of the requested file
  * Date and time of the request
  * Amount of data transmitted
  * Notification of successful request
  * Browser type and version along with the operating system you use
  * Referrer URL
  * Requesting Provider
  * Screen resolution.

The log data is used by us only for statistical analysis in the context of the operation of our offer. In the case of illegal use of our service, the log data also serves to inform a resolution in the eventuality of any violation of the law.

### 2\. Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. On behalf of the website provider Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under [this link.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

This website and its sub-pages exclusively sends shortened (i.e. anonymized) IP addresses to Google.

### 3\. "Facebook-Connect" (Login via Facebook)

The offer provides an alternative to immediate registration, by giving users the opportunity to Login via an existing user account on Facebook (Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA „Facebook-Connect“).

You can take advantage of this by clicking the “Login with Facebook” button and logging into your Facebook account once you have been forwarded. For the registration and utilization of the offer via a Facebook account, Facebook’s own privacy policy as well as Terms of use should be considered in supplementary effect. You can learn about which data is transmitted from Facebook to us, by reading Facebook’s applicable privacy policy. The data here can comprise “public” Facebook profile data, particularly the username, your profile and cover image, your sex, your networks, your age group, your country, your language, the number of “Facebook Friends” as well as any information which you share with your Facebook friends. You partially restrict the transmission of Facebook data by going to Facebook’s privacy settings.

You can revoke the connection between our Website and your Facebook profile by utilizing the appropriate settings in your Facebook user account.

For more information on Facebook-Connect and their privacy policy, please consult the privacy policy and terms of use of Facebook Inc.

### 4\. Liability for Links

Our offer contains Links to websites of external providers. The referred domains were checked at the time of the placement of the link. Their content are not and will not become part of our offer. Should we become aware that the content behind a link has changed and become illegal, we will remove the link automatically.

## IV. Right to Information

To a reasonable extent, you can demand to be informed by us about which personal data we have stored concerning yourself, free of charge.

## V. Changes, Corrections and Updates, Revocation

You have the right to ask for the review and update of your data if you can not do so yourself. You can also have your personal data locked and deleted if they are not subject to statutory retention obligation. The data is also deleted, if you revoke your permission for storage, or the storage of the data is no longer possible due to legal reasons. Given consent for the future collection, processing and utilization of your personal data can be revoked by sending an email to the following address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
